<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-15T09:42:02+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Mark Black</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Book: 100 diskoi kai i istoria tous</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2020/03/21/book-100-diskoi-kai-i-istoria-tous/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Book: 100 diskoi kai i istoria tous" /><published>2020-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2020/03/21/book-100-diskoi-kai-i-istoria-tous</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2020/03/21/book-100-diskoi-kai-i-istoria-tous/">&lt;p&gt;The booklet &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;100 δίσκοι και η ιστορία τους&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (translation: &lt;em&gt;100 records and their story&lt;/em&gt;) was prepared by the
producers and editors of the &lt;em&gt;Μελωδία&lt;/em&gt; (translation: &lt;em&gt;Melody&lt;/em&gt;) radio station and distributed with the issue of
newspaper &lt;em&gt;Καθημερινή&lt;/em&gt; (translation: &lt;em&gt;The Daily&lt;/em&gt;) of 2003-06-29. It contains 100 short chapters, each telling the
story behind the creation of a Greek record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve made a list of the 100 records referenced in this booklet, see:
&lt;a href=&quot;/books/80fc378a-a553-46e3-b45c-bdd21d28eaf2/?100 δίσκοι και η ιστορία τους&quot;&gt;100 δίσκοι και η ιστορία τους&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The booklet 100 δίσκοι και η ιστορία τους (translation: 100 records and their story) was prepared by the producers and editors of the Μελωδία (translation: Melody) radio station and distributed with the issue of newspaper Καθημερινή (translation: The Daily) of 2003-06-29. It contains 100 short chapters, each telling the story behind the creation of a Greek record.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TV Series: To minore tis avgis</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/posts/2020/03/16/tv-series-to-minore-tis-avgis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TV Series: To minore tis avgis" /><published>2020-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/posts/2020/03/16/tv-series-to-minore-tis-avgis</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/posts/2020/03/16/tv-series-to-minore-tis-avgis/">&lt;p&gt;TV series “Το μινόρε της αυγής” (“To minore tis avgis”) ran for 2 seasons in 1983 and 1984. Most of the main characters
in the series are musicians, and so there is a lot of music in every episode. All episodes are available to watch at
the ERT Archive. I have compiled a list of episodes with links to watch them at &lt;a href=&quot;/tv-series/90b29f05-ec37-427c-b8fc-e09cdd4e28b3/?Το μινόρε της αυγής&quot;&gt;Το μινόρε της αυγής&lt;/a&gt;. Further, in
the page for every episode I have noted the songs that play in that episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some more information and cast details see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0327334/&quot;&gt;To minore tis avgis&lt;/a&gt; on IMDB.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">TV series “Το μινόρε της αυγής” (“To minore tis avgis”) ran for 2 seasons in 1983 and 1984. Most of the main characters in the series are musicians, and so there is a lot of music in every episode. All episodes are available to watch at the ERT Archive. I have compiled a list of episodes with links to watch them at Το μινόρε της αυγής. Further, in the page for every episode I have noted the songs that play in that episode.</summary></entry></feed>